Welcome back to Hermy's HQ,
where we just added Forge Labs.
Now, currently,
forge has three new intake forms,
which is why you can see it's glowing right now.
So we're gonna go ahead going to Forge Labs,
which will take us into the systems architect department
that has blueprint, relay,
pulse, echo, Ember.
And we have an extra Ember down here, so.
But are five sub agents.
We have gotten three new intake blueprint forms
that are waiting for us to check out at the Blueprint Center,
which if you click right here,
it'll take us there.
But that's gonna show a lot of businesses information,
and I don't want to bring that up right now,
but if you guys want to make an AI ecosystem just like this,
man, let me know in the comments.
Or fill out the intake form.